MEGAN WEAVER

Junior UI/UX Designer

email weavermeganmarie@gmail.com phone (651) 472-2257 address Minneapolis,MN

About Me

A Junior UI/UX Designer with demonstrated proficiency in research methods from the perspective of an artist, biologist, and designer. A history of creative practice as a fine artist and freelance designer. And the technical ability to translate my ideas into physical products as seen in my participation in four studio art exhibitions and a diverse portfolio of UI/UX Design case studies.

Education

University of Minnesota / September 2020 - March 2021 / Certificate in UI/UX Design

Gustavus Adolphus College / September 2015 - June 2019 / BA in Biology and Studio Art

Awards

Graduated Cum Laude from Gustavus / Voted President of the Gustavus Ski Team / Purchase Award Recipient from Gustavus Art Department / Selected to serve as Teaching Assistant for Gustavus Biology and Chemistry departments

Skills

Adobe XD / Figma / Excel / InVision / HTML5 / CSS / Color Theory / Typography / Iconography / Storyboarding / User Interviews / Surveys / Heuristic Evaluation / UI Grids and Composition / Leadership / Collaboration / Communication / Time Management / Organization / Budgeting

Employment

Wold Architects and Engineers / January 2020 - December 2020 / Administrative Coordinator

- Technical writing
- Standardization of professional documents
- Work collaboratively with team of five
- Liaison between architects, engineers, clients, and contractors
- Professional communication via email, phone, Zoom, and in person meetings

Wilderness Canoe Base / May 2018 - November 2019 / Wilderness Canoe Guide

- Lead groups of students and adults on week long remote wilderness canoe trips
- Communicate effectively with students, adult leaders, camp directors, and healthcare professionals to ensure safe trips
- Facilitate conversations between students from a diversity of backgrounds on conservation, compassion, faith, and unity
- Cultivate a safe and welcoming environment for all students

Employment (cont.)

Gustavus Adolphus College Chemistry and Biology Departments / September 2018 - June 2019 / Teaching Assistant

- Lead student laboratories
- Provide timely feedback on student reports and academic inquiries
- Analyze research results for statistical significance using SigmaPlot
- Professional communication with professors, lab technicians, and students to ensure safe and efficient labs